d2h.com 2019-05-08

# d2h DTH Services - Privacy Policy

## d2h  Privacy policy

**Information Collected**

In general, you can visit this Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Some other information collected by our server includes the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses of the visitor’s computer which connects it to the internet. Our web servers collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses, of visitors. In addition, there are portions of this Web site where we may need to collect personal information from you for a specific purpose, such as to provide you with certain information you request. The information collected from you may include your name, address, telephone, fax number, or e-mail address, etc.

This Web site is not intended for persons under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children, and we do not knowingly market our products or services to children

**Use of collected Information**

Domain name information that we collect is not used to personally identify you and instead is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc. We use this information to measure the use of our site and to improve its content.

When other information is collected from you, such as your name and e-mail address, we generally let you know at the time of collection how we will use the personal information. Usually, we use the personal information you provide only to respond to your inquiry or to process your request (such as to receive newsletters). This information may be shared with other group companies, but, only if necessary, to fulfil your request or for related purposes.

The information collected from you may also be helpful in relation to the services offered by us on our website and also to anticipate and resolve problems with any goods or services supplied to you. Your information is also helpful in administering or otherwise carrying out our obligations in relation to any agreement you have with us and to create products and service to meet your needs. We also use your information to process and respond to requests, improve our operations and communicate with visitors about our products, services and businesses.

In addition, we may have collected similar information from you in the past. By entering this website you are consenting to the terms of our information privacy policy and to our continued use of previously collected information. By submitting your personal information to us, you will be treated as having given your permission for the processing of your personal data as set out in this policy.

We may share the personal information you provide with other companies we have hired to provide services for us. These companies - our vendors - are contractually bound to use personal information we share with them only to perform the services we have hired them to provide. We do not share, sell, or lease personal information about you to any third parties for their marketing use. We will release information about you if you direct us to do so, if we are required by law to do so, or in other legally limited circumstances (for example, to protect your account from fraud).

If you register with one of the Company’s business units online, they may use this information to provide you with custom information about the Company’s offerings in support of your business needs. You should review the privacy policy associated with that the Company business' Web site for further information about that the Company’s business' privacy practices. For example, a technology called cookies may be used to provide you with tailored information. A cookie is a tiny element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie.

**Security of collected Information**

We maintain strict physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to protect your personal information from unauthorized or inappropriate access. We restrict access to information about you to those Company’s employees who need to know the information to respond to your inquiry or request. Employees who misuse personal information are subject to disciplinary action.

**Access to Collected Information**

You may review and update the information that you provide to us through this Web site by contacting us as described below.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please use the Contact Us page. We welcome your questions and suggestions about our privacy policy.

**Changes to this Policy**

Please check this privacy policy to inform yourself of any change. Any site that you may connect to from here is not covered by this privacy policy.
